Asian Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Asian Painting Photograph Collection
1900-2005
VRC 3
Yale University Arts Library
35.4
85 boxes
Collection of mounted black and white and color reproductions of Asian paintings. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Conditions Governing Access
These materials are stored offsite at the Library Shelving Facility. For access to the materials, please make a request at the Art & Architecture Library.
Arrangement
Arranged by country or region. The country or region is further divided by chronological period and individual artists.
Scope and Contents
Collection of mounted black and white and color reproductions of Asian paintings. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Painting -- Asia, Central; Painting -- China; Painting -- Japan; Painting -- India; Photographs; Reproductions
- 7027 photographs.
  - Miscellaneous works., 56 (Box 1)
  - Chou Dynasty., 9 (Box 1)
  - Han Dynasty., 17 (Box 1)
  - Six Dynasties., 48 (Box 2)
    - Unknown artists., 25 (Box 2)
    - Known artists., 23 (Box 2)
      - Ku-K'ai-Chih, 335/344-406., 23 (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous locations., 1 (Box 2)
        - London., 22 (Box 2)
  - Sui Dynasty., 2 (Box 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings.
    - Known artists., 2 (Box 2)
      - Chan Tzu-Ch'ien, active c.581-609., 1 (Box 2)
      - Chi-Kuo, XVII C., 1 (Box 2)
  - T'ang Dynasty., 148 (Box 2)
    Includes two folders containing abstracts about works in the medium format file.
    - Unknown artists., 28 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous works., 18 (Box 2)
      - Imperial tombs., 10 (Box 2)
    - Known artists., 120 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 16 (Box 3)
        - Chang Hsuan, c.750., 1 (Box 3)
        - Ch'eng Chen-Su., 1 (Box 3)
        - Fan Ch'iung, active IX C., 1 (Box 3)
        - Han Huang, 723-789., 1 (Box 3)
        - Li Cheng, active c.800., 1 (Box 3)
        - Li Ssu-Hsun, 651-716., 2 (Box 3)
        - Tai I, XVIII C., 1 (Box 3)
        - Tai Sung, XVIII C., 1 (Box 3)
        - Wei-Ch'i I-Sung, XVII C., 3 (Box 3)
        - Wei Yen., 1 (Box 3)
        - Wu Lae Tzu, school of., 1 (Box 3)
        - Wu Tao-Hsuan, 700-760., 1 (Box 3)
        - Yen Li-Te., 1 (Box 3)
      - Individual artists., 104 (Box 3)
        - Chang Seng-Yu., 2 (Box 3)
        - Chou Fang, c.780-810., 13 (Box 3)
        - Han Kan, c.750., 15 (Box 3)
        - Li Chao-Tao, active c.670-730., 8 (Box 3)
        - Lu Hung, VIII C., 12 (Box 3)
        - Tiao Kuang-Yin., 10 (Box 3)
        - Wang Wei, 699-759., 27 (Box 3)
        - Wu Tao-Tzu, active c.720-760., 4 (Box 4)
        - Yang Sheng., 6 (Box 4)
        - Yen Li-Pen, -673., 7 (Box 4)
  - Five Dynasties., 191 (Box 4)
    - Unknown artists., 26 (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous works., 13 (Box 4)
      - Retreats in the Spring Hills, handscroll., 13 (Box 4)
    - Known artists., 165 (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous artists., 8 (Box 5)
        - Chao Yen, -922., 1 (Box 5)
        - Ch'ui Wen-Po, active c.933-965., 1 (Box 5)
        - Hu Hai, c.930., 2 (Box 5)
        - Li Po., 1 (Box 5)
        - Li Sheng, active c.908-925., 1 (Box 5)
        - Wang Chi-Han, X C., 1 (Box 5)
        - Wei Hsien, X C., 1 (Box 5)
      - Individual artists., 157 (Box 5)
        - Chao Kan, c.970., 14 (Box 5)
        - Ch'en Hung, active 730., 6 (Box 5)
        - Ching Hao, c.900., 14 (Box 5)
        - Chou Wen-Chu, c.970., 20 (Box 5)
        - Hsu Hsi, c.961-975., 8 (Box 5)
        - Huang Ch'uan, -965., 14 (Box 5)
        - Huang Chu-Ts'ai, 933-995., 7 (Box 6)
        - Ku Hung-Chung., 3 (Box 6)
        - Kuan-Hsiu, 832-912., 5 (Box 6)
        - Kuan T'ung, c.907-923., 13 (Box 6)
        - Kuo Chung-Shu, active c.960., 23 (Box 6)
        - T'eng Ch'ang-Yu, c.845-after 930., 3 (Box 6)
        - Tung Yuan, X C., 27 (Box 6)
  - Liao Dynasty., 7 (Box 7)
  - Sung Dynasty., 1619 (Box 7)
    - Unknown artists., 296 (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 31 (Box 7)
      - Boston., 4 (Box 7)
      - Kansas City., 23 (Box 7)
      - Kyoto., 22 (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous Works., 6 (Box 8)
        - Sixteen Lohan., 16 (Box 8)
      - New Haven., 25 (Box 8)
      - New York., 23 (Box 8)
      - Taichung., 183 (Box 9-, Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous works., 166 (Box 10)
        - Old Scholars Meeting., 17 (Box 10)
      - Washington., 7 (Box 10)
    - Known artists., 1323 (Box 10–11)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 108 (Box 11)
        - Ai Hsuan, XI C., 2 (Box 11)
        - Chang Fu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chang Hsun-Li., 2 (Box 11)
        - Chang Mao, active c.1190., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chang Tun-Li., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Ch'iung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao K'o-Hsiung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao K'uei, 1186-1266., 3 (Box 11)
        - Chao Meng-Chien, 1199-1295., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Po-Su., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Pu-Chou., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Shih-Lei., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Ta-Heng., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Ta-Nien, active c.1070-1100., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chao Yuan-Chang., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ch'en Chih-Kung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chen So-Weng., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ch'en Yung-Chich., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ch'i Hsu, X C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chia Shih-Ku, active c.1130-1160., 2 (Box 11)
        - Chih-Weng., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chou Wen-Chu, c.970., 2 (Box 11)
        - Chu Chih-Kuei., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chu Hsi., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chu Kuang-P'u., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ch'u Ting, c.1023-1056., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chu Tz'u-Chung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Chung Jen, XI C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Fan An-Jen, c.1255., 2 (Box 11)
        - Feng Ta-Yu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Feng Tao-Chen., 1 (Box 11)
        - Han Yu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hao Ch'eng., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hsia Shen., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hsiao Chao, XII C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hsiao Yung, active c.1030-1055., 2 (Box 11)
        - Hsu Ch'ung-Ssu, XI c., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hsu Tao-Ning, c.1000-1050., 1 (Box 11)
        - Hsu Ti., 1 (Box 11)
        - Huang Ch'i., 1 (Box 11)
        - Huang T'ing-Chien, 1045-1105., 2 (Box 11)
        - Je-Kouan., 1 (Box 11)
        - Kao Tao., 1 (Box 11)
        - Kao-Tsung, 1127-1162., 1 (Box 11)
        - Kuo Chung-Shu, c.920-977., 1 (Box 11)
        - Kuo Ssu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Kuo-Lung Shang, XI C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Li., 1 (Box 11)
        - Li Chao-Ch'ing., 1 (Box 11)
        - Li Kung-Nien, active c.1100., 2 (Box 11)
        - Li Te-Mao., 1 (Box 11)
        - Li Tsung-Kuei, XIII C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Li Tung., 2 (Box 11)
        - Lien Fu., 2 (Box 11)
        - Lin Huang., 1 (Box 11)
        - Lo Ch'uang., 1 (Box 11)
        - Lo Kuan., 1 (Box 11)
        - Lou Kuan., 2 (Box 11)
        - Lu Hsin-Chung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Lu Tsung-Kuei, XIII C., 2 (Box 11)
        - Ma Fen., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ma Shih-Jung, active c.1130-1160., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ma Yung-Chung., 1 (Box 11)
        - Mao I., 3 (Box 11)
        - Mou Chung-Fu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Pi Liang-Shih., 1 (Box 11)
        - Sun Chih-Wei, active c.1000., 1 (Box 11)
        - Sun Tai-Ku., 1 (Box 11)
        - Sung-Chu., 1 (Box 11)
        - Sung Ti, XI C., 2 (Box 11)
        - T'ang Hsi-Ya., 1 (Box 11)
        - Ts'ai Chao., 1 (Box 11)
        - Tsui Ch'ueh, XI C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wang Ning, XI C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wang Hsi Meng, active 1119-1125., 2 (Box 11)
        - Wang Ting-Kuo., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wang T'ing-Yun, 1151-1202., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wang Yen-Shou, XIII C., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wei Hsien, X C., 2 (Box 11)
        - Wei Sheng., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wu-Chun, c.1175-1249., 1 (Box 11)
        - Wu Chun-Ch'en., 1 (Box 11)
        - Yen-Sou, XIII C., 3 (Box 11)
        - Yen Su, active c.998-1040., 2 (Box 11)
        - Yen Tz'u-Yu, c.1163., 1 (Box 11)
        - Yu Tzu-Ming., 1 (Box 11)
      - Individual artists., 1215
        - Chang Shen-Wen, XIII C., 54 (Box 12)
        - Chang Tse-Taun, XII C., 30 (Box 12)
        - Chao Ch'ang, XI C., 8 (Box 13)
        - Chao Kuang-Fu, active 960-975., 6 (Box 13)
        - Chao Ling-Jang, active c.1070-1100., 9 (Box 13)
        - Chao Po-Chu, active c.1130., 15 (Box 13)
        - Chao Po-Chih,1053-1110., 5 (Box 13)
        - Chao T'ing, 1085-1147., 5 (Box 13)
        - Ch'en Chu-Chung, c.1205., 15 (Box 13)
        - Ch'en Jung, XIII C., 19 (Box 13)
        - Chiang Shen, XII C., 11 (Box 13)
        - Chiang Ts'an, active 1100-1150., 7 (Box 13)
        - Ch'iao Chung-Ch'ang, XII C., 7 (Box 14)
        - Chou Chi-Ch'ang, active c.1163-1180., 13 (Box 14)
        - Chu Jan, c.980., 25 (Box 14)
        - Chu Jui, XII C., 10 (Box 14)
        - Fan K'uan, 950-1026., 27 (Box 14)
        - Fan Lung, active first half 12th century., 4 (Box 14)
        - Hsi-Chin Chu-Shih., 10 (Box 14)
        - Hsia Kuei, active c.1195-1230., 99 (Box 14–15)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 18 (Box 15)
          - Kansas City., 16 (Box 15)
          - New Haven., 12 (Box 15)
          - Taichung., 53 (Box 15)
            - Miscellaneous works., 16 (Box 15)
            - Pure and Remote View of Stream and Hills., 20 (Box 15)
            - Ten Thousand Miles of Yangtze River., 16 (Box 16)
            - Watching the Clouds at Pine Cliff., 1 (Box 16)
        - Hsu Tao-Ning, XII C., 15 (Box 16)
        - Hu Shun-Ch'en, XII C., 8 (Box 16)
        - Hui-Ch'ung, XI C., 6 (Box 16)
        - Hui Tsung., 46 (Box 16)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 21 (Box 16)
          - Taichung., 25 (Box 16)
        - I Yuan-Chi, -1065., 6 (Box 17)
        - Kao K'o-Ming, XI C., 5 (Box 17)
        - Kung K'ai, active c.1260-1280., 4 (Box 17)
        - Kuo Hsi, c.1020-1090., 51 (Box 17)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 18 (Box 17)
          - New York., 10 (Box 17)
          - Taichung., 14 (Box 17)
          - Washington D. C., 9 (Box 17)
        - Li An-Chung, c.1090-1160., 8 (Box 17)
        - Li Ch'eng, c.916-967., 22 (Box 17)
        - Li Kung-Lin, c.1040-1106., 87 (Box 18)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 21 (Box 18)
          - Princeton., 34 (Box 18)
          - Taichung., 22 (Box 18)
          - Washington D. C., 10 (Box 18)
        - Li Shan, c.1250., 14 (Box 18)
        - Li of Shu-ch'eng., 10 (Box 19)
        - Li Sung, c.1190-1230., 22 (Box 19)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 6 (Box 19)
          - Taichung., 16 (Box 19)
        - Li T'ang, c.1050-1130., 52 (Box 19)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 12 (Box 19)
          - Taichung., 40 (Box 19)
            - Miscellaneous subjects., 24 (Box 19)
            - Wen Chi's Return to China., 16 (Box 19)
        - Li Ti, c.1100-1197., 18 (Box 19)
        - Liang K'ai, c.1140-1210., 18 (Box 20)
        - Liang Shih-Min, XII C., 2 (Box 20)
        - Lin Ch'un, active c.1175-1200., 9 (Box 20)
        - Liu Sung-Nien, active c.1195-1224., 32 (Box 20)
        - Liu Ts'ai., 6 (Box 20)
        - Liu Yung-Nien, c.1020-., 8 (Box 20)
        - Ma Ho-Chih, c.1130-1180., 69 (Box 21)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 2 (Box 21)
          - London., 10 (Box 21)
          - Taichung., 47 (Box 21)
            - Miscellaneous works., 7 (Box 21)
            - The Book of Filial Piety., 25 (Box 21)
            - Ladies' Hsiao-ching., 15 (Box 21)
        - Ma K'uei, active c.1180-1220., 5 (Box 21)
        - Ma Lin, XIII C., 25 (Box 21)
        - Ma Yuan, active c.1190-1224., 74 (Box 22)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 24 (Box 22)
          - Shanghai., 8 (Box 22)
          - Taichung., 42 (Box 22)
            - Miscellaneous works., 35 (Box 22)
            - Collection of Small Paintings., 7 (Box 22)
        - Mi Fei, 1051-1107., 6 (Box 22)
        - Mi Yu-Jen, 1086-1165., 19 (Box 22)
        - Mou I, c.1178-1243., 14 (Box 23)
        - Mu-Ch'i., 31 (Box 23)
        - Su Han-Ch'en, XII C., 12 (Box 23)
        - Su Shih, 1036-1101., 12 (Box 23)
        - Ts'ui Po, XI C., 12 (Box 23)
        - Wang Hung, c.1150., 25 (Box 23)
        - Wang Li-Yung, active first half 12th century., 3 (Box 24)
        - Wang Shen, active c.1050-1100., 42 (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 7 (Box 24)
          - New York., 16 (Box 24)
          - Shanghai., 6 (Box 24)
          - Taichung., 13 (Box 24)
        - Wen T'ung, -1079., 4 (Box 24)
        - Wu Ping., 5 (Box 24)
        - Wu Yaun-Chih, c.1195., 11 (Box 24)
        - Yang Shih-Hsien., 4 (Box 24)
        - Yang Wu-Chiu, XII C., 4 (Box 24)
        - Yeh Hsiao-Yen., 5 (Box 24)
        - Yen T'zu-P'ing, active c.1165-1181., 4 (Box 24)
        - Yen Wen-Kuei, 967-1044., 28 (Box 24)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 22 (Box 24)
          - Taichung., 6 (Box 24)
  - Yuan Dynasty., 982 (Box 24)
    - Unknown artists., 125 (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 48 (Box 25)
        - Miscellaneous works., 30 (Box 25)
        - Kuang-Sheng-Ssu Temple., 18 (Box 25)
      - Taichung., 60 (Box 25)
      - Washington., 17 (Box 25)
    - Known artists., 857 (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 70 (Box 26)
        - Chang Shun-Tzu, active 1330-1350., 2 (Box 26)
        - Chang Tzu-Cheng., 1 (Box 26)
        - Chang Yen-Fu, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Chang Yu, 1275-1348., 1 (Box 26)
        - Chao Hsi-Yuan., 1 (Box 26)
        - Chao Lin, XIV C., 4 (Box 26)
        - Ch'en Chen, active c.1350., 1 (Box 26)
        - Ch'en Chung-Jen, active c.1300., 2 (Box 26)
        - Ch'en Ju-Yen, active 1340-1380., 2 (Box 26)
        - Ch'en Li-Shan, active c.1350., 1 (Box 26)
        - Cheng Ssu-Hsiao, 1239-1316., 3 (Box 26)
        - Chu Shu-Chung, active c.1365., 2 (Box 26)
        - Chuang Lin, XIV C., 2 (Box 26)
        - Fang Yai, active c.1360., 1 (Box 26)
        - Han Tao-Heng and Lu Yuan-Su., 1 (Box 26)
        - Hsia Yung, active 1340s., 2 (Box 26)
        - Hsieh Po-Ch'eng, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Hu T'ing-Hui, active c.1300., 1 (Box 26)
        - Kang Li-K'uei., 1 (Box 26)
        - Ku Te-Hui, 1310-1369., 2 (Box 26)
        - Kuan Tao-Sheng, 1262-1325., 2 (Box 26)
        - Kung K'ai, 1222-1307., 1 (Box 26)
        - Kuo Min., 1 (Box 26)
        - Lai An, 1280-1368., 1 (Box 26)
        - Li Sheng, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Lin Chuan-A., 1 (Box 26)
        - Liu Kuan-Tao, active c.1270-1330., 3 (Box 26)
        - Liu Shan-Shou., 1 (Box 26)
        - Liu Yuan, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Lo Chih-Ch'uan., 1 (Box 26)
        - Lu Hsin-Chung., 1 (Box 26)
        - Lu Kuang, active c.1325., 3 (Box 26)
        - Ma Liang, 1280-1368., 1 (Box 26)
        - Pa-Yen Pu-Ha., 1 (Box 26)
        - Pien Wu., 1 (Box 26)
        - Sa-Tu-La, active c.1315-1340., 1 (Box 26)
        - Shang Ch'i, active c.1295-1345., 2 (Box 26)
        - Sun Chun-Tse., 2 (Box 26)
        - Sung K'o, 1327-1387., 2 (Box 26)
        - Tai Ch'un., 1 (Box 26)
        - T'ao Fu-Ch'u, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wang Chung-Yu, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wang I., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wei Chiu-Ting, active c.1350-1370., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wei Tao Jen., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wu T'ai-Su, XIV C., 1 (Box 26)
        - Wu T'ing-Hui., 1 (Box 26)
        - Yang Wei-Chen., 2 (Box 26)
        - Yin-T'o-Lo., 1 (Box 26)
      - Individual artists., 787 (Box 26)
        For paintings by Hsueh Ch'uang see: P'u Ming, China, Yuan.
        - Chang Shou-Chung., 6 (Box 26)
        - Chang Wu, active 1335-1365., 8 (Box 26)
        - Chao Ch'i., 4 (Box 26)
        - Chao Meng-Fu, 1254-1322., 86 (Box 27)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 16 (Box 27)
          - New York., 12 (Box 27)
          - Taichung., 58 (Box 27)
            - Miscellaneous works., 20 (Box 27)
            - Autumn Colors on the Mountains., 11 (Box 27)
            - Hsiao-ching (Book of Filial Piety)., 10 (Box 27)
            - Rivers and Peaks., 17 (Box 27)
        - Chao Yuan, active c.1370., 11 (Box 28)
        - Chao Yung., 9 (Box 28)
        - Ch'en Lin, c.1260-1320., 3 (Box 28)
        - Cheng Hsi, active c.1350., 7 (Box 28)
        - Ch'ien Hsuan, 1235-c.1300., 105 (Box 28)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 30 (Box 28)
          - J. C. Ferguson Collection., 10 (Box 28)
          - Detroit., 7 (Box 28)
            - Early Autumn., 7 (Box 28)
          - Peking (Peiping, Beijing)., 14 (Box 29)
          - Taichung., 28 (Box 29)
            - Miscellaneous works., 18 (Box 29)
            - Peony handscroll., 5 (Box 29)
            - Waiting for the Ferry at the Misty River., 5 (Box 29)
          - Washington D. C., 16 (Box 29)
        - Chu Te-Jun, 1294-1365., 5 (Box 29)
        - Fang Ts'ung-I, active c.1340-1380., 22 (Box 29)
        - Ho Ch'eng., 8 (Box 29)
        - Huang Kung Wang, 1264-1354., 35 (Box 30)
          - Miscellaneous works., 12 (Box 30)
          - Dwelling in the Fu-Ch'un Mountains., 23 (Box 30)
        - Jen Jen-Fa, 1254-1327., 20 (Box 30)
        - Jen Po-Wen., 7 (Box 30)
        - Kao K'o-Kung, c.1245-1310., 22 (Box 30)
        - K'o Chiu-Ssu, 1290-1343., 5 (Box 31)
        - Ku An, active c.1330., 5 (Box 31)
        - Kuan Tao-Sheng, 1262-c.1325., 4 (Box 31)
        - Kuo Pi, 1280-1335., 7 (Box 31)
        - Li K'an, 1245-1320., 10 (Box 31)
        - Li Jung-Chin., 3 (Box 31)
        - Li Shih-Hsing., 17 (Box 31)
        - Ma Wan, active 1325-1365., 6 (Box 31)
        - Meng Yu-Chien., 7 (Box 31)
        - Ni Tsan, 1301-1374., 67 (Box 32)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 18 (Box 32)
          - Taichung., 49 (Box 32)
            - Miscellaneous works., 24 (Box 32)
            - Miscellaneous bamboo paintings., 15 (Box 32)
            - Painting studies, album., 10 (Box 32)
        - P'u Ming., 4 (Box 32)
          Also known as Hsueh Ch'uang.
        - Sheng Mou, active c.1310-1360., 25 (Box 32)
        - T'ang Ti, 1296-1364., 8 (Box 33)
        - Teng Tzu-Fang., 9 (Box 33)
        - Ts'ao Chih-Po, 1272-1355., 15 (Box 33)
        - Tsou Fu-Lei., 16 (Box 33)
        - Wang Chen-P'eng., 30 (Box 33)
        - Wang Meng, c.13008-1385., 67 (Box 33)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 16 (Box 33)
          - Peking (Peiping, Beijing)., 7 (Box 33)
          - Taichung., 24 (Box 34)
        - Wang Mien, 1335-1407., 16 (Box 34)
        - Wang Yuan, active c.1329., 6 (Box 34)
        - Wu Chen, 1280-1354., 68 (Box 34)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 13 (Box 34)
          - Taichung., 55 (Box 34)
            - Miscellaneous subjects., 19 (Box 34)
            - Bamboo Album, dated 1350., 25 (Box 34)
            - Ink Bamboo, album., 11 (Box 35)
        - Wu Po-Li., 6 (Box 35)
        - Yao T'ing Mei, active c.1360., 14 (Box 35)
        - Yen Hui., 14 (Box 35)
  - Ming Dynasty., 2312 (Box 35)
    - Unknown artists., 139 (Box 35)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 36 (Box 36)
      - New York., 13 (Box 36)
      - Princeton., 10 (Box 36)
      - Taichung., 26 (Box 36)
      - Washington D. C., 54 (Box 36)
    - Known artists., 2173 (Box 36)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 187 (Box 36)
        - Chan Ching-Feng., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Ch'ih., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Chi Su., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chang Han., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chang Jui-T'u, died after 1640., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Ling, c.1470-1520., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Meng-Kuei., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Ning., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chang Yuan-Shih, active c.1570., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Chia-Yen, active c.1600., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Chia-Yen., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Hsien, XVII C., 2 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Huan., 3 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Kuan., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chen Tien-Hsien., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'en Tzu-Ho, c.1500., 3 (Box 37)
        - Cheng Min, 1607-1682., 1 (Box 37)
        - Cheng Shih., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'eng Sui, 1605-1691., 3 (Box 37)
        - Chiang Ch'ien., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chiang Kuei., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chiang Sung, active XVI C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ch'iu Shih, active c.1550., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chou Ch'uan, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chou Wei., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chou Wen-Ching., 3 (Box 37)
        - Chou Yung., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chu ?., 2 (Box 37)
        - Chu Fei., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chu Lang, active c.1540., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chu Lu, 1553-1632., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chu Mou-Shih, active c.1600., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chu Pang., 4 (Box 37)
        - Chu Yin, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chung Ch'in-Li, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Chung Li, c.1460-1500., 3 (Box 37)
        - Fan I-Chih, 1611-1671., 3 (Box 37)
        - Ho-Shan-Lao-Ch'iao., 3 (Box 37)
        - Hou Mou-Kung, XVI C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsia Ping, active c.1450., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsiang Te-Hsin, XVII C., 2 (Box 37)
        - Hsaio Hai-Shan., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsiao Tseng, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsieh Chin, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsieh Huan, active 1426-1452., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsien Tsung, 1448-1487., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsing Ts'e-Ching., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsing Tz'u-Ching., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsu Ching, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsu I, active c.1640., 1 (Box 37)
        - Hsu Tuan-Pen, 1438- after 1517., 1 (Box 37)
        - Huang Shao-Ming., 2 (Box 37)
        - Hou Mou-Kung, active XVI C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Huang Tao-Chou, 1585-1646., 4 (Box 37)
        - Ku I-Te, XVII C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ku Ning-Yuan, active c.1636., 1 (Box 37)
        - Kuo Tien., 1 (Box 37)
        - Leng Ch'ien., 1 (Box 37)
        - Li Sheng, active mid-XIV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Li Tsai., 2 (Box 37)
        - Li Tsung-Ch'eng., 1 (Box 37)
        - Lin Hsueh, active 1627., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Chieh, active c.1485-c.1525., 2 (Box 37)
        - Liu Ch'un or Chao Ch'i, c.1450., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Fang., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Shih-Ju, XVI C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Tu., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Yao, XIV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Liu Yuan-Ch'i, active c.1620-1633., 2 (Box 37)
        - Lu Chi, c.1500., 1 (Box 37)
        - Lu Ching-Fu, XIV C., 2 (Box 37)
        - Lu Fu, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Lu T'ren-Fu, active c.1427., 1 (Box 37)
        - Lu Tuan-Chun., 1 (Box 37)
        - Lu Wen-Ying, c.1500., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ma Chun., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ma Shih, XV C., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ma Shih-Ta., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ma Shou-Chen, active c.1592-1628., 2 (Box 37)
        - Ma Shou-Chen, active c.1600-1620., 1 (Box 37)
        - Mi Wan-Chung, 1570-1628., 1 (Box 37)
        - Mo Shih-Lung, active c.1567-1600., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ni Hung-Chih Pieh., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ni Tuan., 1 (Box 37)
        - Ni Yuan-Lu, 1593-., 1 (Box 37)
        - P'an Yu, c.1500., 1 (Box 37)
        - Shen Chen, 1400-after 1480., 3 (Box 38)
        - Shen Ch'uan (Nan-P'in), active c.1725-1780., 1 (Box 38)
        - Shen Hao, 1586-after 1661., 1 (Box 38)
        - Shih Chung., 2 (Box 38)
        - Su Chen., 1 (Box 38)
        - Sun Chih, active c.1550-1580., 2 (Box 38)
        - Sun Ti., 1 (Box 38)
        - Sung Hsu, 1523-1605., 3 (Box 38)
        - Sung Teng-Ch'un., 1 (Box 38)
        - Ta-Hsien., 1 (Box 38)
        - T'ang Chih-Yin., 2 (Box 38)
        - T'ao Hung, XVII C., 1 (Box 38)
        - Ts'ao Miao-Ch'ing, XIV C., 2 (Box 38)
        - Ts'ao Yu-Kuang., 1 (Box 38)
        - Ts'eng Ching, 1568-1660., 1 (Box 38)
        - Tsou Chih-Lin, active c.1645., 2 (Box 38)
        - Tsu-Te, c.1441., 2 (Box 38)
        - Wang Chao, active c.1500., 2 (Box 38)
        - Wang Chi, active c.1600-1637., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wang Ch'ien, XVI C., 3 (Box 38)
        - Wang Chien-Chang, active 1628-1644., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wang Li, XVI C., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wang Shih., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wang Shih-Ch'ang, 1462-after 1531., 3 (Box 38)
        - Wang Shou-Jen., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wang Wei-Lieh, active c.1580., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wen Cheng, 1500-1582., 3 (Box 38)
        - Wen Shu, 1595-1634., 2 (Box 38)
        - Wen T'ai., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wen Ts'ung-Chien, 1574-1648., 2 (Box 38)
        - Wen Yuan-Shan, 1554-1589., 1 (Box 38)